Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nirodavancuylenburg (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Adjustments

VLAN

Packet Switching

Certifications

CCNA: Introduction to Networks

Network Security

CCNA: Enterprise Networking, Security, and Automation

CCNA: Switching, Routing, and

Wireless Essentials

Niroda Vancuylenburg

Network Support Engineer at Exetel

Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Summary

A passionate and highly motivated individual, focused primarily on the development of positive resolutions and relationships. Currently following BSc in Computer Systems & Network Engineering of Curtin University, Australia at SLIIT. Skilled from several experiences in Team leadership, Consulting Correspondence, Client Engagement and Satisfaction as a strong professional.

Experience

Exetel

Network Support Engineer January 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months) Sri Lanka

Jay Jay Mills Lanka (Pvt.) Ltd Junior Executive May 2021 - January 2022 (9 months) Colombo District, Western, Sri Lanka

Hatton National Bank PLC Trainee January 2020 - April 2020 (4 months) Colombo, Western, Sri Lanka

Sampath Bank Internship Trainee June 2019 - November 2019 (6 months) Colombo, Western, Sri Lanka

Education

Curtin University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Network and System Administration/ Administrator · (2018 - 2021)

SLIIT

Bachelor of Science - BS, Network and System Administration/ Administrator · (2018 - 2021)